i'm here with the truth you don't want to hear you don't want to hear it i'm gonna say it you
don't want to hear it but it's gotta be sad you don't want to hear it but it's gotta be excuse me
but it's gotta be sad i'm only talking to the black folks right now i'm only talking to the
black folks right now you don't want to hear it but it's gotta be sad y'all keep saying you know
why we're in this we're in this situation because y'all didn't vote for kamala no you know why we're
in this situation because you niggas is too compliant because we used to be a revolutionary
people and you motherfuckers got so god damn something you know who customer service ends up
paying attention to the folks that are a thorn in their side don't get me wrong they may actually
hold you down and they may actually like show up for you if you're kind and nice and we should be
kind and nice but baby you know who they actually end up paying attention to the folks who stay on
their neck that's who that's who they end up paying the most attention to and every single
and there aren't that many but every single effort at advancement that has been made in this country
for black folks has been when our foot was on necks that's it that's it now to hear folks legit
be thinking well the only way we gonna get anything is if we do what they tell us to do
it's crazy it's crazy that doesn't make any sense y'all there's no evidence that supports that in any
well they said we because it's too compliant very very very go along with the get along
very that very that very listening to your oppressor
and following their instructions very that very that very that so i i hope that you take these words
and think about them because it's really sad to watch people that come from revolution
revolution and radicalism really be on the same nonsense
really be thinking really be lying to themselves and thinking that the system that has never worked
for us is all of a sudden gonna start working for us if we just do what the other people are doing
what it doesn't make sense it doesn't make sense guys so i implore you to consider
well what would be a different mode of action because we can't do the same thing they do
and think it's gonna get the same results it's just it's it's it's so silly it's silly
how did i how did i come how did i put this together before every time i have to reassemble
this it's like the first time i'm always like what did i do before it's silly y'all got too compliant
so people have voted undecided communities got together and voted undecided that happened
and it wasn't just one community if if what you're planning to do is what they expect you to do then it's
not the thing you need to do okay let that marinate if what you're planning to do
is what you're expected to do it's not what you need to do